Knight, Max; Papers ger050
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Clippings of published stories and essays, 1930-1992; 4; 84 file folders
  - Clippings in German, 1930-1938; 4.1
    - "Filmkritik", 1937 February 11 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 9)
    - "Frag mich nichts!", Undated (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 10)
    - "Frauen in der Sommerfrische", 1937 August 6 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 10)
    - "Fuchstreibjagd in Kärnten", 1935 August 27 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 10)
    - "Fünf Schritte lagen dazwischen. Der Skilehrer hat unrecht gehabt", 1937 April 24 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 10)
    - Hans, Dr. Josef. "Gangsters in Chicago. Erlebnis eines Wieners", 1935 January 17 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 11)
    - H., St. "Geschäft in Arabien", 1937 November 28 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 11)
    - "Das Geschäftsprinzip", 1936 March 14 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 11)
    - "Geschichte eines Frauenhaares", 1937 September 10 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 11)
    - "Geschichte eines Liedes", 1937 August 31 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 11)
    - "Geschichte zu viert", 1937 November 16 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 12)
    - "Gesellschaftstelephon", 1937 January 17 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 12)
    - "Geständnisse", 1937 August 7 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 12)
    - Schütz, Mia. "Der Glückspilz", 1937 June 3 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 12)
    - Hanke, Stephan. "Gold oder Liebe? Eine historische Erzählung", 1934 May 1-1934 May 2 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 12)
    - "Das Grabmal des Selim Chistis", 1936 July 28 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 12)
    - "Graf Tagazzi belebt das Weihnachtsgeschäft", 1936 December 29 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 12)
    - "Die große Liebe des Hubert Lanzky", 1937 January 19 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 13)
    - "Großreinemachen!", 1938 January 30 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 13)
    - "Der grünen Sechzehn", 1936 July (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 13)
    - "Der Handschuh", 1936 March 3 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 13)
    - "Hin und zurück", 1937 May (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 13)
    - "Die höhere Warte", 1937 June 26 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 13)
    - "Die ideale Ehe. Humoreske", 1936 April 11 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 14)
    - "Ihr letzter Walzer", 1936 November 5 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 14)
    - "Im Interesse des Schwiegervaters", 1937 October (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 14)
    - Anonymous. "In Lederhosen um Europa", 1938 January 17 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 14)
    - "Indianer als Petroleumkönige", Undated (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 14)
    - "Indien. Wiedersehen in Bombay", 1935 September 18 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 15)
    - "Jack Gregorys letzter Streich", 1936 September 19 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 15)
    - Kühnel, Max Eugen. "Junger Mensch kommt nach Verdun", 1936 January 19 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 15)
    - "Kaiser Josef renkt alles ein", 1936 March 26 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 15)
    - "Die Kiesel der Waganda", 1937 April 6 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 15)
    - "Kleine Tragödie im Stiegenhaus", 1937 August 3 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 16)
    - "Kleine Ursachen", 1937 March 2 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 16)
    - Kühnel, Max Eugen. "Kleine Wunder einer großen Stadt", 1935 June 19 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 16)
    - "Kleines Intermezzo", 1936 May (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 16)
    - "Kleines Lotto", 1936 September (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 16)
    - Kühnel, Max Eugen. "Der Knopf", 1930 February (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 17)
    - "Der Koffer", 1937 February 28 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 17)
    - "Kopf hoch, Jimmy!", 1938 February 22 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 17)
    - "Kreuzwege", Undated (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 17)
    - Kühnel, Max Eugen. "Kristalle der Sprache", 1937 June 30 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 18)
    - "Küß nicht im Kino!", ca. 1936/1937 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 18)
    - "Kunstgeschichte nach Maß", Undated (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 18)
    - "Das Lager von Ahmednagar. Wie ich krieginterniert wurde". Serialization, 1935 October 19-1935 November 23 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 19)
    - "Landstraße", 1935 February 21 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 20)
    - "Der Lebensretter", ca. 1937 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 20)
    - "Lerne biegen!", 1936 September 20 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 20)
    - Anonymous. "Lernet Geschichte!", 1935 October 17 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 20)
    - "Liebe per Blumenkorb", 1938 February 1 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 20)
    - "Liebe per Post", 1937 May 27 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 21)
    - "Lug ins Land", 1936 July 25 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 21)
    - "Lux auf der Spur", 1935 June 22 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 21)
    - "Madelaine", 1935 August 14 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 21)
    - "Mädchen mit Veilchen", 1935 October 3 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 21)
    - F., P. "Märchen-Kobolde im Zeitalter des Telefons", 1938 February 5 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 22)
    - "Der Märchenprinz", ca. 1937 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 22)
    - "Der Maharadscha", Undated (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 22)
    - "Man muss den Frauen imponieren!", 1936 September 20 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 22)
    - "Der Mann aus dem 18. Jahrhundert", 1936 August 1 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 22)
    - "Der Mann mit dem Muttermal", 1937 April (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 22)
    - "Der Mann vor der Auslage", 1937 March 21 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 23)
    - "Mausi und der Frechdachs", 1936 August 26 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 23)
    - "Moderne Turandot", 1936 June (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 23)
    - Hanke, Stephan. "Mord vor zweitausend Zeugen", 1935 August 1 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 23)
    - F., P. "Nur ein Fahrschein ...", 1938 May (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 23)
    - "nur zwei tage ...", 1938 February (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 24)
    - "Der Orden", 1936 July 5 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 24)
    - "Ordination", 1936 August 25 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 24)
    - "Der Paß siegt nach Punkten. Eine Groteske", 1936 February 2 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 24)
    - "Die Probe", 1936 May 19 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 24)
    - "Prüfung mit Handschuhen", 1936 August 20 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 25)
    - "Der Puo-Puostamm", 1936 July 21 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 25)
    - "Radikale Verjüngungskur", 1937 May 14 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 25)
    - "Das Radio", 1936 November 26 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 25)
    - K., Dr. M. E. "Die Rätsel des Papyrus", 1937 September 11 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 25)
    - "Rebellen", 1937 December (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 25)
    - "Regie der Liebe", 1936 November 23 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 26)
    - "Rezept für Liebeskranke", 1936 August 15 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 26)
    - "Der Satyr. Verse", 1937 September (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 26)
    - "Der Schnellverkäufer", 1937 March 11 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 26)
    - "Die schutzlose Frau", 1938 January 13 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 26)
    - "Schwarzfahrt wider Willen", 1938 March 3 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 26)
    - Ellert, Charlotte. "Sein bester Trick", 1937 January 24 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 27)
    - "Der Sekretär", 1937 April (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 27)
    - "Seltsames Erlebnis", ca. 1937/1938 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 27)
    - "Soll man gefällig sein?", 1937 December 31 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 27)
    - "Spiel mit Feuerlilien", ca. 1937 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 27)
    - "Springflut", 1936 November 15 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 27)
    - "Der Sprung über den Weltkrieg", Undated (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 27)
    - "Spuk in der Nacht", Undated (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 27)
    - "Tagebuch eines Nichteifersüchtigen", Undated (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 28)
    - "Takt", 1936 December 14 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 28)
    - "Tante Alice steckt im List ...", 1936 October 30 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 28)
    - "Tanzfest auf Madagaskar", 1937 June 6 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 28)
    - "Der Taugenichts", Undated (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 28)
    - "Timmerton verkühlt sich", 1936 October (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 28)
    - "Das Todesschiff. Die Katastrophe des 'Saint-Philibert'", 1936 April 18 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 29)
    - "Der Traum vom Königstum", Undated (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 29)
    - "Der Trick der Spionin", 1938 April (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 29)
    - Friese, Ernst. "Die Uhr", 1938 March 6 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 29)
    - "Umgang mit Kukuruz", ca. 1938 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 29)
    - "Der unredliche Finder", ca. 1937-1938 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 29)
    - "Unsterbliche Bäume", Undated (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 30)
    - Fregoli. "Der Ursprung des Fußballspiels", Undated (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 30)
    - Epstein, Dr. jur. H. J. "Der vegetarische Löwe", 1936 March 30 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 30)
    - "Verdacht", 1936 March 8 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 30)
    - "Die Verführung", 1935 September 28 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 30)
    - "Vergnügen in der Sommerfrische", 1936 August 30 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 31)
    - "Die verschlossene Tür", Undated (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 31)
    - "Viel Lärm um einen Kanari ...", 1937 September 29 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 31)
    - "Vienna -- Made in U.S.A", 1936 January 31 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 31)
    - Kühnel, Max Eugen. "Von der Engheit des Herzens", 1936 June 10 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 31)
    - "Was halten Sie von der Zigarette?", 1937 May 26 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 31)
    - "Was macht man mit einem verwaisten Handschuh?", 1937 February 13 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 32)
    - Förster, P. "Weihnachtseinkäufe", 1935 December 21 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 32)
    - "Weihnachtszauber", ca. December 1936 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 32)
    - "Die Welt ist voll vom Wundern. Das Zimmer im Baumstamm", 1936 March 21 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 32)
    - "Wenn vier dasselbe tun ...", 1937 May 20 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 32)
    - Fridolin, Paul. "Wirbel am Ferdinand. Original-Roman", November 1936-? (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 33)
    - Kühnel, Max Eugen. "Wo blieb Lord Evan?", 1935 July 28 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 34)
    - "Der Wohltäter", 1936 July 13 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 34)
    - "Der Zigarettenfitscher", 1936 November 29 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 34)
    - "Zwanzig Minuten", 1936 August 6 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 34)
  - Stories and articles written and published in German, 1938-1945; 4.2
    - "Chinesische Studenten lernen englisch und deutsch", 1941 May 7 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 35)
    - F., P. "Denken verboten", 1944 November (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 35)
    - "Denksport", 1939 September 25 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 35)
    - "Ein Lord macht Geschäfte", 1938 October 26 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 35)
    - "Ein Mann mit Humor", 1939 November 16 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 35)
    - "Ein Opfer der Technik", 1939 April 26 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 35)
    - Twin, Oliver. "Der elfte März und die Presse", 1945 March (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 36)
    - "Etui", 1939 February 20 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 36)
    - "Falsch verbunden", 1945 March 31 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 36)
    - "Der Fremdenfuehrer", 1940 November 29 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 36)
    - "Geld, oder die anderen schiessen!", 1940-1941 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 36)
    - "Der gezeichnete Domino", 1939 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 37)
    - "Der größte Fund seines Lebens", 1940 February 24-1940 February 25 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 37)
    - "Der Grotesktänzer", 1940 March 4 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 37)
    - "Der Handschuh", 1940 January 8 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 37)
    - "Kantonesisch essen", 1941 April 4 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 37)
    - F., P. "Oesterreichisches Emigrantenheim in London", 1939 March 24 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 38)
    - "Das plaudernde Tagebuch", 1939 December 22 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 38)
    - "Rikscha-Kulis", 1941 April 17 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 38)
    - Twin, Oliver. "Rund um die San Francisco Konferenz", 1945 June (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 38)
    - "Das Salzfaß", 1940 April 25 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 38)
    - Twin, Oliver. "Sievering in California", 1945 August (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 38)
    - "Die Spur", 1939 May 8 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 39)
    - "Der Tugendbold", 1940 February 25 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 39)
    - Twin, Oliver. "Das ungeschriebene Buch", 1945 April (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 39)
    - Twin, Oliver. "Wenn zwei dasselbe sagen", 1945 November (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 39)
    - Twin, Oliver. "Wiener im letzten Ghetto der Welt", 1945 September (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 39)
    - Twin, Oliver. "Zu ebener Erd' und im ersten Stock", 1945 February (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 39)
  - Stories and essays published in English, 1938-1945; 4.3
    - "A Friend In Need Is A Friend In Deed", 1938 May 28 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 40)
    - "A Husband in Montreal", 1940 August 17 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 40)
    - "A Million Hats" / "Well Done Daisy!", 1937 December 11 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 40)
    - "A Nice Kind Man", Undated (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 40)
    - "A Permit for Aunt Sophie", 1939 September 8 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 40)
    - "A Stitch in Time. War weaves a new pattern for two in love in Norway", 1940 May 17 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 40)
    - "Ali Hussein's Deal", 1939 November 11 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 41)
    - "The Amber Necklace", 1938 March 16 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 41)
    - "Aunt Alice in the Lift", 1937 December 9 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 41)
    - "Business Principles" / "Wireless", 1937 December 8 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 41)
    - "Cheap-Jack", Undated (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 41)
    - "Christmas in the Mountains", Undated (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 42)
    - "Confessions", Undated (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 42)
    - "Counted Out", Undated (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 42)
    - "Courage" / "Anonymous Letter", 1937 October 30 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 42)
    - "The Election and Leonardo da Vinci", 1944 December (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 42)
    - "The First Swallow 1938-1939. Max", Undated (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 43)
    - "Grotesque Dancer", Undated (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 44)
    - "Her Pearls. A Little Ruse Which Did Not Fail", Undated (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 44)
    - Fabry, Peter Joe. "In Professor Freud's London Home", 1941 April (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 44)
    - "Intelligence Test", 1937 December 7 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 44)
    - "Life of a Hair", Undated (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 44)
    - "Little Mirrors of Life. In this Queer Town, Its History and Yours and Mine with It Is Recorded in Unexpected Places", 1941 February 9 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 44)
    - "The Locked Door", 1939 March 31 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 44)
    - "Ludovico's System", 1939 January 24 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 45)
    - "Milton Isn't Enough", 1938 June 11 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 45)
    - "Missing from Home", 1939 July 8 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 45)
    - "Postman's Knock", 1937 November 12 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 45)
    - "Potted Money", Undated (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 45)
    - "The Rag In The Bottle. A Message Which Cleared The Way For A Lover", 1938 September 10 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 45)
    - "Record Ships in Waltz-Time", 1944 January (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 45)
    - Anonymous. "The Refugees in the Vagabonds' State", 1939 February (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 46)
    - Anonymous. "Revolution!", Undated (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 46)
    - "Rolling Snowball" / "Tall Tale", Undated (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 46)
    - Anonymous. "The Romance of Shanghai. Storyteller on Hong List", 1941 February 2 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 46)
    - "Salt-Cellar", 1940 December 15 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 46)
    - "Set to Partners", 1939 November 4 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 47)
    - "Some Store!" / "Flowers for Lily", 1938 March 15 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 47)
    - F., P. "Sonny Stays Home", Undated (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 47)
    - "The Spy's Trick", 1940 March (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 47)
    - "Star Engagement", Undated (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 47)
    - "Stray Glove", 1937 December 6 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 47)
    - Anonymous. "Strolling Down the Bund. A Refugee Compares Shanghai with Other Ports", 1941 March 2 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 47)
    - "Suede Glove Test", Undated (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 48)
    - "The Suit Case", 1938 August 27 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 48)
    - "Swank!", Undated (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 48)
    - "The Talking Fish", Undated (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 48)
    - Fabry, Peter Joe. "There She Goes -- My Wonderboat!", 1943 April (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 48)
    - "Tourist Guide", Undated (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 48)
    - "Won't Any Man Love Me Please!", 1938 March 31 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 48)
  - Publications in English, 1945-1992; 4.4
    - "A Close Look at the Lowly Envelope", Spring 1957 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 49)
    - "A University Celebrates its 600th Birthday", Winter 1966 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 49)
    - Knight, Max. "Adventures in Translation", 1967 September 22 (Box 5 (4-Clippings of published stories and essays), Folder 49)